<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<prefabDesc descVersion="1">
    <author>Farming Dud's</author>
	<contributors>Glowins Modschmiede</contributors>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
	<title>
        <en>Isobus Terminal CCI200</en>
    </title>
	<description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[
Terminal of the "Competence Center ISOBUS". The CCI200 is offered by a variaty of different manufacturers.
You can choose between Lemken, Zunhammer, Kuhn, Krone and Amazone. Each manufacturer has its own field of specialization.
That means every Terminal supports a special device on your machine.

Along to the 3D Modell and its textures comes a second feature of this prefab.
The Terminal fully supports the Dashboard Live Script, published by "Glowins Modschmiede".
The needed xml code is given too. Because of this it is only for PC mods.
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
<![CDATA[
Terminal des "Competence Center ISOBUS". Das CCI200 wird von einer Vielzahl verschiedener Hersteller angeboten.
Sie haben die Wahl zwischen Lemken, Zunhammer, Kuhn, Krone und Amazone. Jeder Hersteller hat sein eigenes Spezialgebiet.
Das heißt, jedes Terminal unterstützt ein spezielles Gerät an Ihrer Maschine.

Neben dem 3D Modell und seinen Texturen gibt es noch ein zweites Feature dieses Prefabs.
Das Terminal unterstützt vollständig das Dashboard Live Script, welches von "Glowins Modschmiede" veröffentlicht wurde.
Der benötigte xml-Code ist ebenfalls enthalten. Aus diesem Grund ist es nur für PC-Mods geeignet.
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
<![CDATA[
Terminal du "Competence Center ISOBUS". Le CCI200 est proposé par plusieurs de  fabricants différents. 
Vous avez le choix entre Lemken, Zunhammer, Kuhn, Krone et Amazone. Chaque fabricant a sa spécialité propre. 
Cela signifie que chaque terminal appartient à une machine spécifique.

Inclus dans le prefab ne sont pas seulement les modèles 3D et les textures correspondantes mais les terminals 
supportent entièrement le Dashboard Live Script, qui a été publié par "Glowins Modschmiede".
Parce-que le code xml nécessaire pour le fonctionnement du script est également inclus le prefab ne convient qu'aux mods PC.
]]>
		</fr>
    </description>
	<categories>
        <category>Other</category>
    </categories>
	<brands>
        <brand name="Isobus" title="ISOBUS" image="brand_isobus.dds"/>
    </brands>
	<iconFilename>icon_CCI200.dds</iconFilename>
	<prefabs>
		<prefab name="CCI200 Terminal" i3dFilename="Isobus_CCI200_Terminal.i3d" />
    </prefabs>
</prefabDesc>